[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "How difficult was it to find them and in the end, what was the key breakthrough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "The difficulty in finding them Piers is really being able put the right resource in the right area using both community resources and train resources around the state, put them in the right spot at the right time to find them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What happened next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, some period of time during the course of the traveling through this dirt roads and snow in some pretty rural area.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Does it surprise you that he was so quick thinking and possibly saved their lives in that way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "He's a smart guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Are they expected from what you understand to make a complete and full and speedy recovery?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "I would expect that they would make a full recovery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "And in terms of your advice Paul for anybody watching who maybe exposed to similar treacherous conditions, almost I guess the first bit of advice is if you can avoid going out and stay at home but if you are out and you do get caught like this, what is the recommendation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "They did the exact thing that they should.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "In terms of their cellphone, there was, we believe a signal but it wasn't strong enough for them to make any calls out but it was strong enough to be able to track it, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "That's correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "NN", ":", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "You were part of this, did you have fears start to increase as the hours went by that you may not have a happy ending to all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, I never want to thought -- nobody wanted to think that at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Tell me a little bit more if you can, Jo Ann about the family what kind of family are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Oh, well they're a (good) family, you know, like I said they -- he was a good friend to my son in high school and they're still friends and just a close knit family, you know, all the kids they do everything together, you know, they're good people with good heart, you know, and they're close to their family and that was the important thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jo Ann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "And that moment Paul when you heard that it was good news and they were alive and well, there was must be one of the most satisfying parts of your job isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "It's what we call the psychic income.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "... is that OK with you?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last Sunday"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", ":", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Is he, as it seems to be really this guy that's get sick and tired of hours of shopping and deliberately takes his life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "We may never know the full story here but it does appear that some of these pressures of shopping -- holiday shopping contributed to this man's tragic and fatal decision of last Sunday to jump off the seventh floor balcony of this shopping mall.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Why do women make men go to shopping?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "What are you spending (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I love the fact that you're buying lovely shoes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lululemon"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "I mean, was there a policy by the stores, the Lululemon stores to actively deter larger ladies from coming in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "JJR", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Well, the store that I actually worked at Lululemon makes a size 12 yoga pant which is considered the lower end of plus size and those pants are actually not displayed with the other sizes on the store wall.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lululemon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heather Thomson"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Is this what people do in this game and are they targeting the yoga pants at a slimmer woman perhaps, and we just don't want to admit it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Certainly not a Yummie by Heather Thomson.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "How are you both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Howard"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "How do it start?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "I can only take Howard in doses.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":"], "qSentId": 310, "question": "It's not mistaken, you have never been spoon-fed guacamole by Eva Longoria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "But ...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eva Longoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States", "United States"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "How difficult is it to make real inwards into that level of hunger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Well, it's extremely difficult but the difference between the United States and many other places we were is it's doable in the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Well it's a combination isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "... them to perform well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "What is the single most effective thing that could be done for Latino community?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "ONGORIA: Education is the single most important thing that can be done because education is the key to economic mobility.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "How helpful is it to you to have Ms. Longoria who is -- let's face it aesthetically very appealing to the media?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Well, I think it goes way beyond that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ms. Longoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "It's used for good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "This is a big issue in America, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "CD", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What is the answer to this particular part of the puzzle, the minimum wages?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "UFFETT: Well, you know, you just back up one step and say that, only the solution to pulling people out of poverty making sure they're fed is to have them working.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "What is going wrong at the moment with Obama Incorporated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Well, you know, in regards to ObamaCare, nothing is wrong with ObamaCare.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Obama Incorporated"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "You're disappointed that it was done so badly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Did you get your hands dirty, Eva?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "You know what, I grew up on a farm.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eva"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "So basically, it's easy farming, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "He was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "When are you going to do this for a living?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I think I'm not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Was that supposed a no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "ONGORIA: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Do you think she should though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Or would it be a great moment as was the ascent of Barack Obama, for African-American in America would be a great moment for the Latino community to see it even if it wasn't your side of the fence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Pano right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Pano.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Just one of you maybe the next superstar of sport in America, so how are you all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Good.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "So you four are the best young golfers in the world, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "CD", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "So who's the best on the four you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Obviously me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Allan"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Do you play each other boys with the girls or no, is it always kept separate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "There in tournaments, it's kept separate but when we do our practice turns, I always play against Allan and I always take him down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "That's about seven times in a row that I beat you, is that correct?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Just because she maybe beats me in the practice rounds, I do beat her in tournament days every single time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Is that how you feel about playing golf?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Absolutely, because when you hit the golf ball you just get a good vibe or a good feeling in your body.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Do you think that's changing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "I think, yeah, it is changing because they always in tournaments say, OK girls can play shorter distances than guys because they can't hit it as far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alexis Thompson"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "And when I played with Alexis Thompson (ph) and she could out drive all the people that we were playing with and with no problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "The top female golfers only make around $2.5 million, do you think that's unfair, should you all get paid the same?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "$", "CD", "CD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I think we should get paid the same because girls can do anything boys could do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$2.5 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Where would spend it on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Well, I'll probably buy a mansion in California.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anna Kournikova"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Now, Allan you're full -- you got all the chat, right which is not surprising because you got a very famous sister, who is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Anna Kournikova.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Allan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Do you use to beat your a sister at anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "In golf, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "But not in tennis, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "What does it mean to you to play golf?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Well, it's just the fun of the game just to play and I love the game and its fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "What does he mean to you, Nelson Mandela?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "He's a good -- he's a legend of South Africa and I know he is an -- he was a very good man and when he was in jail for 27 years he gave peace and freedom to our country.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nelson Mandela"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "And are you proud to represent South Africa in golf?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Do you think you can be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP"], "qSentId": 648, "question": "You're up for it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Yup", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Is this for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "(inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]